a-ads.net 2011-04-08

# Privacy Policy - Active Ads - Paid To Click

[Home](http://a-ads.net/en/) | Privacy Policy 

A-Ads is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the A-Ads website and governs data collection and usage. By using the A-Ads website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

## Collection of your Personal Information

A-Ads collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. A-Ads also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favourites. There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by A-Ads. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by A-Ads for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the A-Ads website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through A-Ads public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others

  * A-Ads does not read any of your private online communications.
  * A-Ads encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from A-Ads so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. 
  * A-Ads is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the A-Ads and A-Ads family of websites.

## Use of your Personal Information

A-Ads collects and uses your personal information to operate the A-Ads website and deliver the services you have requested. A-Ads also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from A-Ads and its affiliates. A-Ads may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

A-Ads does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. A-Ads may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, A-Ads may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to A-Ads, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

A-Ads does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent. A-Ads keeps track of the websites and pages our customers visit within A-Ads, in order to determine what A-Ads services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customised content and advertising within A-Ads to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

A-Ads websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that
